{
	"poetry": [
        {
            "Question": "Ah, To Eat At All Is Such A Foolish Game. Eating Huckleberry Pie",
            "Answer": "Is A Pleasing Way To Die",
        },
        {
            "Question": "And David’s Lips Are Lock’t; Rbut In Divine Rhigh Piping Pehlevi, With",
            "Answer": "Wine! Wine! Wine!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "And He Played Upon A Ladle, A Ladle, A Ladle, Rand He Played Upon A Ladle, Rand His Name Was Aiken Drum.",
            "Answer": "And His Hat Was Made Of Good Cream Cheese",
        },
        {
            "Question": "And I Am Happier Than You Are, Rand They Were Happier Than I Am; Rand The Fish Swim In The Lake",
            "Answer": "And Do Not Even Own Clothing.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "And The Sugar-Plums Tumble, Of Course, To The Ground–",
            "Answer": "Hurrah For That Chocolate Cat!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "And To Keep Out The Cold I’ve Bought A Cloak Rand Every Day A Cigar I’ll Smoke, Rall To Follow My Own Dear True",
            "Answer": "Love Of A Kangaroo!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "As I Was Going To St. Ives, Ri Met A Man With Seven Wives, Reach Wife Had Seven Sacks,",
            "Answer": "Each Sack Had Seven Cats",
        },
        {
            "Question": "As I Went To Bonner, Ri Met A Pig Rwithout A Wig,",
            "Answer": "Upon My Word And Honour",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Ba-Ba, Black Wool Rhave You Any Sheep? Ryes, Sir, A Packfull",
            "Answer": "Creep, Mouse, Creep!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Barber, Barber, Shave A Pig Rhow Many Hairs Will Make A Wig? Rfour And Twenty; That’s Enough.",
            "Answer": "Give The Poor Barber A Pinch Of Snuff",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Bobby Shafto’s Looking Out, Rall His Ribbons Flew About,",
            "Answer": "All The Ladies Gave A Shout",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Brow, Brow, Brinkie, Reye, Eye, Winkie, Rmouth, Mouth, Merry,",
            "Answer": "Cheek, Cheek, Cherry",
        },
        {
            "Question": "But Four Young Oysters Hurried Up, Rall Eager For The Treat: Rtheir Coats Were Brushed, Their Faces Washed Rtheir Shoes Were Clean And Neat – Rand This Was Odd, Because, You Know,",
            "Answer": "They Hadn’t Any Feet",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Close Your Eyes, Poppies Ri Would Not Have You See Death. Ryou Are So Young!",
            "Answer": "The Sun Falls Like A Drop Of Blood",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cock A Doodle Do! Rmy Dame Will Dance With You,",
            "Answer": "While Master Fiddles His Fiddlingstick",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Cock A Doodle Do! Rwhat Is My Dame To Do? Rtill Master’s Found His Fiddlingstick,",
            "Answer": "She’ll Dance Without Her Shoe",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Dance To Your Daddy, Rmy Little Babby; Rdance To Your Daddy, Rmy Little Lamb. Ryou Shall Have A Fishy,",
            "Answer": "In A Little Dishy",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Do Not As Children Badly Bred Rwho Eat Like Little Hogs Rand When They Have To Go To Bed",
            "Answer": "Will Whine Like Puppy Dogs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Do Not As Evil Children Do Rwho On The Slightest Grounds",
            "Answer": "Will Imitate The Kangaroo",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Hands, Do What You’re Bid: Rbring The Balloon Of The Mind Rthat Bellies And Drags In The Wind",
            "Answer": "Into Its Narrow Shed",
        },
        {
            "Question": "He Died A Hard Death Long Ago Rbefore The Road Came In Rthe Night Before He Swung,",
            "Answer": "He Sang To His Mandolin.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "He Saw The Laughter Ron My Lips,",
            "Answer": "And Only Kissed My Finger-tips",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Here Comes A Candle To Light You To Bed, And Here Comes A Chopper",
            "Answer": "To Chop Off Your Head",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Here’s A Creature, Young And Slender, Rdrest In Robes Of Dazzling Splendor, Rin A Chariot Decked With Gold; –",
            "Answer": "She’s The Fairy Queen I’m Told",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Know Very Well What I’d Like To Do Rif I Didn’t Have To Do What I Do!",
            "Answer": "I’d Go And Be A Woodpecker",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Know Very Well What I’d Rather Be Rif I Didn’t Always Have To Be Me!",
            "Answer": "I’d Rather Be An Owl",
        },
        {
            "Question": "I Make Truce With You, Walt Whitman Ri Have Detested You Long Enough. Ri Come To You As A Grown Child Rwho Has Had A Pig-Headed Father;",
            "Answer": "I Am Old Enough Now To Make Friends.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "If Wished Were Horses, Beggars Would Ride Rif Turnips Were Watches,",
            "Answer": "I Would Wear One By My Side",
        },
        {
            "Question": "If You Are To Be A Gentleman, As I Suppose You’ll Be, Ryou’ll Neither Laugh Nor Smile",
            "Answer": "For A Tickling Of The Knee",
        },
        {
            "Question": "In These Days Of Indigestion Rit Is Oftentimes A Question Ras To What To Eat And What To Leave Alone; Rfor Each Microbe And Bacillus",
            "Answer": "Has A Different Way To Kill Us",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Jack’s Mother Came In, Rand Caught The Goose Soon, Rand Mounting Its Back",
            "Answer": "Flew Up To The Moon",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Johnny Watched The Swallows Trying Rwhich Was Cleverest At Flying",
            "Answer": "Oh! What Fun!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Little Nancy Etticote, Rin A White Petticoat, Rwith A Red Nose; Rthe Longer She Stands,",
            "Answer": "The Shorter She Grows",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Little Robin Redbreast Rcame To Visit Me; Rthis Is What He Whistled,",
            "Answer": "Thank You For My Tea",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Little Tommy Tittlemouse Rlived In A Little House; Rhe Caught Fishes",
            "Answer": "In Other Men’s Ditches",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Molly, My Sister, And I Fell Out, Rand What Do You Think It Was About? Rshe Loved Coffee, And I Loved Tea,",
            "Answer": "And That Was The Reason We Couldn’t Agree",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Nimble Little Monkey, Tony, Rrides Along Upon A Pony, Rfollowed By A Stupid Clown",
            "Answer": "Who Thinks The Rain Is Pouring Down",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Now, Just Imagine How It Feels Rwhen First Your Toes And Then Your Heels, …. Are Slowly Eaten, Bit By Bit. No Wonder Jim Detested It!",
            "Answer": "No Wonder That He Shouted, \”hi!\”",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Old Father Long-Legs Rcan’t Say His Prayers: Rtake Him By The Left Leg,",
            "Answer": "And Throw Him Downstairs",
        },
        {
            "Question": "One Mist Moisty Monring, Rwhen Cloudy Was The Weather, Ri Met A Little Old Man,",
            "Answer": "Clothed All In Leather",
        },
        {
            "Question": "One Step More! Oh! Sad To Tell! Rheadlong In Poor Johnny Fell. Rand The Fishes, In Dismay",
            "Answer": "Wagged Their Tails And Swam Away",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Pussy Sits Beside The Fire. Rhow Can She Be Fair? Rin Walks A Little Doggy,",
            "Answer": "Pussy, Are You There?",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Shall Sit By My Side Rand I’ll Give Her Some Food; Rand Pussy Will Love Me",
            "Answer": "Because I Am Good.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Went To The Barber’s Rto Buy Him A Wig Rwhen She Came Back",
            "Answer": "He Was Dancing A Jig",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Went To The Hatter’s Rto Buy Him A Hat, Rbut When She Came Back",
            "Answer": "He Was Feeding The Cat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Went To The Tailor’s Rto Buy Him A Coat, Rbut When She Came Back",
            "Answer": "He Was Riding A Goat",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Went To The Tavern Rfor White Wine And Red; Rwhen She Came Back",
            "Answer": "The Dog Stood On His Head",
        },
        {
            "Question": "She Went To The Undertaker’s Rto Buy Him A Coffin; Rwhen She Came Back",
            "Answer": "The Dog Was Laughing.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Snail, Snail, Come Put Out Your Horn,",
            "Answer": "Tomorrow Is The Day To Shear The Corn",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Talents Differ; All Is Well And Wisely Put; Rif I Cannot Carry Forests On My Back,",
            "Answer": "Neither Can You Crack A Nut.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Captain Was A Duck, Rwith A Packet On His Back; Rand When The Ship Began To Move,",
            "Answer": "The Captain Said, Quack! Quack!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Clever Men At Oxford Rknow All There Is To Be Knowed. Rbut They None Of Them Know One Half As Much",
            "Answer": "As Intelligent Mr Toad!",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Dame Made A Curtsy, Rthe Dog Made A Bow; Rthe Dame Said, Your Servant;",
            "Answer": "The Dog Said, Bow-wow",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Hen Sat Quietly At Home, Rthe Cock Sang Merrily; Rand All The Little Young Ones Said,",
            "Answer": "Wee, Wee, Wee, Wee, Wee, Wee",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The King Of Spain’s Daughter Rcame To Visit Me, Rand All For The Sake",
            "Answer": "Of My Little Nut Tree",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Maid Was In The Garden, Rhanging Out The Clothes; Rby Came A Little Bird,",
            "Answer": "And Snapt Off Her Nose",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Sea Was Was Wet As Wet Could Be, Rthe Sands Were Dry As Dry. Ryou Could Not See A Cloud,",
            "Answer": "Because No Cloud Was In The Sky",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Vulture Eats Between His Meals Rand That’ The Reason Why Rhe Very, Very, Rarely Feels",
            "Answer": "As Well As You And I.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "The Walrus And The Carpenter Rwere Walking Close At Hand; Rthey Wept Like Anything To See",
            "Answer": "Such Quantities Of Sand",
        },
        {
            "Question": "There Was An Old Crow Rsat Upon A Clod. Rthere’s An End Of My Song,",
            "Answer": "That’s Very Odd",
        },
        {
            "Question": "There Was An Old Woman Rlived Under A Hill, Rand If She’s Not Gone,",
            "Answer": "She Lives There Still",
        },
        {
            "Question": "There’s A Cat Named Joe And You Wouldn’t Want To Know But He Thinks",
            "Answer": "He’d Like To Be A Hippopotamus",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Three Wise Men Of Gotham Rwent To Sea In A Bowl; Rif The Bowl Had Been Stronger",
            "Answer": "My Story Had Been Longer",
        },
        {
            "Question": "To Educate Young Spiders Rshe Took Me All Apart Rmy Ghost Came Back To Haunt Her",
            "Answer": "I Saw Her Eat My Heart",
        },
        {
            "Question": "Up Jack Got And Home Did Trot, Ras Fast As He Could Caper; Rand Went To Bed And Bound His Head",
            "Answer": "With Vinegar And Brown Paper",
        },
        {
            "Question": "We Were Young Plants Growing Rto Brave The Cold! Rthe Gold Sun Kissed You All The Winter —",
            "Answer": "I Am Old.",
        },
        {
            "Question": "What Is Green? The Grass Is Green, Rwith Small Flowers Between. Rwhat Is Violet? Clouds Are Violet Rin The Summer Twighlight. Rwhat Is Orange?",
            "Answer": "Why An Orange, Just An Orange!",
        }
    ]
}